Zack, Arnold Additional Arbitration Files 5727
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
1972-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold
5727
16 cubic feet
16 linear ft.
Records.
3123460
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 08, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 24, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5281: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5512: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5551: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5620: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5659: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5727: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial--United States--Sources.; Zack, Arnold.
3123460
- Adams County - Bulletin Co.. (Box 1)
  - Adams County 120, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams County School District 50 AAA/Dal 7139-0214-80, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alaska Airlines, AFA Seattle June 3, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ARA Food Services/ Local 274 Philadelphia, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Arlington School Committee (greivance) 1139-2015-81 April 6, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Associated Grocers and IBT, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Associated Grocers and Teamsters, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Auburn Maine Central Vocational Tech, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Baltimore County - TABCO Dept. Ch-Auto Driv, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Baltimore County and TABCO, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Barre Granite Association and Cutters Assignment of Drafting Work, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Barrington and Police AAA/Boston. 1139-1694-79, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bedford School Committee 1139-1486-81 Bedford, Ma. 11/2/81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Beacon Press and SEIU #925 AAA/Boston. 1130-0872-80, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bedford, New Hampshire, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Boston University and AAUP AAA/Boston. 1130-1836-79, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Boulder Colo/ Board of Education And BVEA Jan. 6 and 7, 1981 Fact-finding (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Boulder Valley Public Schools Education Association Mediation. 12/8-9/81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Town of Brookline and AFSCME, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Town of Brookline/MTA Mediation Nov. '82, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bulletin Co. 1430-0804-79 S, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Cleaver Brooks - Framingham Polio. (Box 2)
  - Cleaver Brooks and Leb'n Ind. Un. 1430-1221-81, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Colorado Springs October 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts And AFSCME, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts and AFSCME, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts And AFSCME, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts D.S.S./ Alliance OER Grievance, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts (Department of Corrections) CA-606, OER 80-149, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts - MNA, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts/ MNA Greivance. OER 81-52 2/8/82, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts and SEIU 509 - 549 OER, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Continental and ALPA ALPA Cal-8-79, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Town of Danvers/AFSCME Interest Arbitration Oct. 82, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Department of Defense and Overseas Education Association. 1/25-29, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - DEA - Frankfurt, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Dover, NH Mediation 1982/83, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dunham-Bush, Inc./IAMAW Hartford, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - IUE Promotions Gr. 14-30-1584-81 Philadelphia., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Fafnir and UAW 133, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Framingham Fire Department AAA 1139-0642-79, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Town of Framingham/, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Frontier Airlines - Greyhound. (Box 3)
  - Frontier Airlines and AFA AFA 44-36-1-107-79, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Frontier Airlines and AFA 11/14/80, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Frontier Airlines/AFA Denver, CO., 1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Georgia Pacific and UPIU AAA/BOS 30-1853-79, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Greyhound - 12/12/80, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Greyhound Buffalo, NY Discharge, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Greyhound/ATU Discharge. Boston, Ma. 4/30/81, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Greyhound/ATU Discharge Minneapolis April 14, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Greyhound and Amalgamated Transit Union; Miami, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Greyhound and ATU Philadelphia. 2/26/81, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Greyhound and Amalgamated Transit Union New York City Jan 27, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Greyhound/ATU Greivance. Philadelphia, PA., 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Harvard - Iberia Airlines. (Box 4)
  - Harvard Comm. Health Plan 1130-0594-81 6/29/81, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Harvard University/Local 26, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hershey Foods Hershey, Pa., 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Hershey and Choc Workers, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hershey Foods/Chocolate Workers, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Hershey Disability-pregnancy, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hershey - Related Illness Disability, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hershey, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Hershey, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hershey and Local 1464, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hershey Foods/Local 464, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Hershey Foods/Local 464 Dress Room Case, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Hershey, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Hershey Machine Storeroom, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hershey, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hershey Pregnancy Disability, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Howard County Teachers AAA/Philadelphia 1430-1158-790, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Horace T. Potts Co. 1430-1329-81 Philadelphia, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Iberia Airlines/IAMAW 3-81, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Iberia Airlines/IAMAW Grievance, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound
  - Iberia Airlines/IAMAW Grievance, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Iberia Airlines/IAMAW Grievance, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Iberia Airlines/IAMAW Grievance, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Iberia Airlines/IAMAW Grievance, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Johnston - New England. (Box 5)
  - Johnson, R.I. School Committee/AFT 1139-2379-81, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Keshwick and Health Care Employees 1199E AA/Phil 1430-1049-79B, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Lansdale (borough of) and Molders 1430-1570-80 R, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Geo. Leno/Warehouse Employees. Discharge. Philadelphia., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Geo Lane and Warehouse Employees, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Londonderry School Board./ NHEA Londonderry, NH, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Long Island University/Local 3998, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - State of Maine and MTA William Files SM 79-2, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Manchester, New Hampshire, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Manchester, NH and NHEA Mediation, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts Transit and Transit Workers AAA/Phil, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts Transit and Amalgamated Transit Union 1300 AAA/Phil., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Medical College and 1199c AAA/Philadelphia 1430-1374-79R, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan Hospital and District 1199C AAA/Philadelphia., 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Middlesex and AFSCME AAA/Boston, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Metropolitan Hospital/1199 Philadelphia, Pa., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Middlesex County Jail and IBPO 493 AAA/Boston., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - NASHUA City and Firefighters, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - NFTA and Amalgamated Transit Union AAA/Syracuse., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - New England Consortium of State Labor Relations Agencies, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- New Hampshire - New York City. (Box 6)
  - Greyhound and Transit 2/8/80 - Indianapolis, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Misc., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - State of N.H./ SEA Mediation/ FF Dec., 2,6,20,21,22, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - NYC PBA I-130-77, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - LBA Exhibits, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NYC Sba BCB 320-79, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - City Exhibits, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- New York City. (Box 7)
  - SBA Exhibits, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - NYC and SBA LBA and OMLR (Police Office), 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Joint Exhibits, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - City of Newport/AFSCME 1139-2434-81, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - North Providence School Committee and Teachers 1138-1653-80, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Sergeants' Benevolent Association of the Police Department of the City of New York, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The City of New York -and- Sergeants Benevolent Association of the Police Department of the City of New York and Lieutenants Benevolent Association, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sergeants Benevolent Association of the Police Department of the City of New York and Lieutenants Benevolent Association, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The City of New York -and- Sergeants Benevolent Association of the Police Department of the City of New York, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - The City of New York -and- Sergeants Benevolent Association of the Police Department of the City of New York and Lieutenants Benevolent Association, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - The City of New York -and- SBA, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - The City of New York -and- SBA, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - The City of New York -and- SBA, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - The City of New York -and- SBA, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - The City of New York -and- SBA, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - The City of New York -and- SBA, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - The City of New York -and- SBA, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - The City of New York -and- SBA, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - New York City OCB 5/20/80, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Newport - Plymouth Rubber. (Box 8)
  - Northwest Airlines and BRAC 11/4/80 Seattle Smoking Case, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Northwest/IAM - Feb. 24, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Northwest Airlines/IAM Oct. 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - NWA/IAM (Discharge #82-50), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Northwest Orient/IAM, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - NWA-IAM, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - NWA/IAMAW, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Northwest/IAMAW, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Old Rochester School Committee/Professional Education Association Fact Finding (Mass.) Oct. 1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Okonite and IBEW AAA/BCS 1130-0462-80, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Pan Am/IUFA New York City Oct. 26-27, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Peabody Light and AFSCME #364 AAA/BCS 1139-0877-80, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Peabody Store Fixtures and Local 82 RA-3-1981- Commonwealth of Massachusetts (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Plymouth Rubber and URW 573 AAA/Boston. 1130-2147-79, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Pan AM/ALPA greivance. JFK Airport, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Proctor & Gamble - Riverside Rest Home. (Box 9)
  - Procter and Gamble, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Procter and Gamble/Chemical Workers Eliz/ NJ Jet Port, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Providence School Committee/ Teachers, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Providence School Committee Teachers 3/24/1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Pueblo, Co. and Teachers Association AAA/Dallas, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Pueblo, Colorado Dec. 1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - PATCO and FAA June 4, 1980 Bedford, Ma. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - PATCO (Plane Count), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - PATCO and FAA, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - State of Rhode Island and AFSCME AAA/Boston 1139-1803-79, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - State of Rhode Island and AFSCME 314 AAA/Boston. 1139-0334-80, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - State of Rhode Island and AFSCME AAA/Boston 1139-0432-80, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - State of Rhode Island and AFSCME 1350 AAA/Boston 1139-0400-80, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Rhode Island and AFSCME 5/81, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - State of Rhode Island/ AFSCME 1139-1021-81 Providence, R.I., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - State of Rhode Island, AFSCME 1139-1693-81, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - State of Rhode Island./ Empl. Sec. Alliance 1139-1569-81, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Riverside Rest Home/1199 Dover, NH (2479-81), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - TWA-IAM Greivance. 52985-ORD, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - TWA and ALPA, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - TRW Bearings/UAW Hartford, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Union Carside and OCAW Gr. 327-120-78 Training Fenwal System, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - University of Massachusetts and AFSCME AAA/Boston 1139-0953-79, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Umass and AFSCME 2616 AAA/Boston 1139-0863-80, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Umass and Massachusetts Society of Professors. AAA/Boston 1139-1989-79, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Umass - 1139-1989-79, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Cleveland Transcripts Volumes 10 and 11 Riccards Testimony, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Rochester Telephone Co. - TWA. (Box 10)
  - Rochester Telephone Corp/CWA Rochester, NY, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Rutherford County Education Association., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - St. Vrain Valley School District, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Schaeffer and Brewer Workers 1010 AAA/Phil 1430-1837-78J, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Sinai Hospital- 1979-3222, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Somerset Schools AAA/Boston 1139-1965-79, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Table Talk and Bakery Workers 251 RA-8-80 (Commonwealth of Massachusetts), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Texas International A/L and ALPA Alberta Wekenborg Gr., 1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Texas International Airlines/ ALPA Houston, Texas, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Thinsheet Metal and USS AAA/Hartford 1230-0421-79, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Texas International, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - TWA - Pilots Association Greivance. June 1-2, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Transworld/IAM New York - 1/9/80 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- TWA - U. Mass. (Box 11)
  - TWA and IAM Grievance #52985-ORD, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    April 29, 1981
  - TWA and ALPA LAX [folder 1 of 4], 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - TWA and ALPA LAX [folder 2 of 4], 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - TWA and ALPA LAX [folder 3 of 4], 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - TWA and ALPA LAX [folder 4 of 4], 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - TRW Bearings and UAW Grievance #1230-0048-82, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Hartford, CT.
  - Union Carbide and OCAW Grievance #327-120-78, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Training Fenwal System
  - UMass and AFSCME 2616, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    AAA/Boston #1139-0953-791979-1980
  - UMass and AFSCME 2616, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    AAA/Boston #1139-0863-80
  - UMass and Massachusetts Soceity of Professors [folder 1 of 3], 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    AAA/Boston #1139-1989-79
  - UMass and Massachusetts Soceity of Professors [folder 2 of 3], 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - UMass and Massachusetts Soceity of Professors [folder 3 of 3], 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - UMass and Grievance #1139-1985-79 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts volumes 10-11, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Riccards testimony
  - UMass and Grievance #1139-0399-80 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Umass and Tenure Grievance #1139-0449-80, 1979-1983 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - UMass [folder 1 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - UMass [folder 1 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 18)
- U. Mass. - U.S. Postal Service (USPS)/APWU Grievance Arbitsation. (Box 12)
  - Agreement Between Board of Trustees of the University of Massachusetts, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - American Arbitration Association Commonwealth of Massachusetts, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - American Arbitration Association - University of Massachusetts, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - American Arbitration Association - University of Massachusetts, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - University of New Haven and FAC Welfare 3956 AAA/Hartford 1239-0344-79, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - UAL 12-80, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - United Airlines/AFA Chicago, Illinois May 20 and 21, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - United Airlines/AFA Chicago Sept. 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - UAL and Flight Attends SFO 5-78:, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - United Airlines and Flight Attendants Den 22-79, Den 15-80: McCaddon, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - UAL and Flight Attendants SFO 11-78 9/18/79, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - United Airlines: Flights Attendants LAX 11-80, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - United Airlines and Flight Attendants SFO 61-74, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - United Airlines and Flight Attendants SFO 65-74, 1972-1976 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - UAL - Ord 22-80, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - United Airlines and Flight Attendants Ord. 6-80 4/17/80, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - United Airlines and Flight Attendants Ord 63-79, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - United Illuminated and Utility Workers 470, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - USPS/APWU Gr. Hartford 4/23/82, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - USPS 11/7/81, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Collective Bargaining City of New York, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- USPA/APWU - Grievance Arbitration. (Box 13)
  - USPS and APWU, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - USPS/APWU 50/673/D Boston - Discharge, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - USPS/APWU Boston, Ma., 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - USPS, 1974-1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - USPS and APWU, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - USPS-APWU Cad0221- Remedy, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - USPS/APWU Greivance., 1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - USPS/APWU Greivance., 1982 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - USPS and APWU 110-11-1105-D, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - USPS/APWU New York City 9/24/82, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - USPS-APWU New York City, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Postal Service Discharge NYC, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - USPS and APWU N&C-IN-D8075-D., 1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - USPS/APWU Greivance., 1981 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - USPS 9/24/82, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - USPS-APWU, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - USPS/APWU Grievance 4/15/81, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - USPS/APWU (NIT-1E-C 501), 1982 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - USPS/APWU 1C-1J-D 4836 New Haven, CT 9/16/82, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Postal Service - Boston Discharge 3/3/81, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - USPS/APWU Boston Discharge, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - U.S. Postal Service And APWU, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - USPS/APWU New Haven CT, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - USPO and APWU, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - USPS and APWU, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- USPA/APWU - Grievance Arbitration (Portland) - USPS/APWU Interest Arb. w/ ADPC & PDC. (Box 14)
  - USPS/APWU Portland, ME (2 Cases) 10/15/82, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Portland, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - USPS/APWU N8C-IM-D 14223 New York, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - USPS/APWU N8C-IM-D 14223, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - USPS/APWU Manchester, NH, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - USPS/APWU NYC, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - USPS/APWU Hartford, CT 10-29-82 Grievance, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - USPS/APWU Grievance N8C-1E-D 20438 Boston 11/5/81, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - USPS/APWU Grievance N8T-1E-D 20463 Dec. 3, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - USPS-APWU N8C-1J-D, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - USPS and APWU, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - USPS A, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - USPS/APWU Feb. 16-17, 1982 San Juan, P.R. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - USPS/APWU, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - USPS/APWU (2 Cases) New Haven, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - U.S.P.S./A.P.W.U. Grievance (CAN-18414) Peabody, Ma. 11/4/81, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - USPS/ADPC Interest Arbitration 4/9/82, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Union Exhibits, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Union Exhibits, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - UJPJ + APWA - Interest Arbitration, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- USPS/APWU - Interest Arbitration w/ ADPC & PDC - USPA/NALC. (Box 15)
  - USPS + APWA, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - United States Postal Service -and- American Workers Union, AFL-CIO Employees of the Postal Data Centers, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - USPS and APWA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - USPS -and- APWA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - USPS -and- APWS, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - USPS and APWA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - USPS - APWA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - USPS - APWS, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - USPS - APWA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - USPS - APWA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - USPS - APWA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - USPS - APWA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - USPS - APWA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - USPS - APWA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - USPS - APWA, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - USPS and CLIUNA, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - USPS and LIUNA N8M-IE-C 4347 et al., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - USPS/Mailhinders Gadson Gr. Springfield, Ma., 1982 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - USPO and Letter Carriers, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - USPO and Letter Carriers, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - USPS/NALC Pawtucket, RI Nov, 24. 1982 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - USPS/NALC Boston, Mass. Grievance 4/15/82, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - USPO - NALC, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - USPO and NALC N8N-1A-D2457, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - USPS/NALC June 4, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - USPS and NALC - N8N-1A-D 4664, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - USPS/NALC Boston 20019, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - USPO and NALC #2259, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - USPS /2978 Grievance., 1982 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- USPC/NALC - Yarmouth. (Box 16)
  - USPO and NALC 1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - USPS-NALC New York City 6/10/81, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - USPS and NALC, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - NALC/USPS 12418 Grievance, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - USPS/NALC South Hadley, Ma, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - USPS/NALC Mt. Vernon, NY, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - USPS and NALC, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Postal Service/ NALC Grievance Boston 6/9/82, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - USPS/NALC Grievance Albany, N.Y. 3/19/82 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - USPS NALC, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - USPS/NALC Glens Falls, NY, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - USPS N8N- IK D 15543 9/24/81, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - USPO and NALC, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - United Parcel and Teamsters 331 AAA/Philadelphia 1430-0863-80J, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Upjohn Company Carwin Employees 3/27/81, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Upjohn ompany Carwin Employees, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Valley Gas Co./UWUA Cumberland, R.I., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - State of Vt./ V.S.E.A. Nov. 11, 12, 13, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Western Kraft Paper/ Local 497 1430 1854 81Q Philadelphia., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Western Mass. Elec. And IBEW Chicopee, Ma., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 20)